Guide to Bryn Mawr College Catalogs, etc. Cubb.00296
Cubberley Education Library
Bryn Mawr College
1884-1978
Cubberley Education Library
Cubb.00296
266 item(s) Programs for 1885/86-1888, 1891-1907/08 Calendars for 1908-1928 Calendars for undergraduate courses for 1929-1975/76, 1977/78
Located in Bryn Mawr, Pennsylvania. Founded in 1885 as a Quaker college for women. In 1931, Bryn Mawr began accepting men as graduate students, while remaining women-only at the undergraduate level.
Women's colleges -- United States; Pennsylvania
- President's Reports, 1884-1942; 17 item(s) Reports for 1884-1885/86, 1888/89-1892/93, 1894/95-1897/98, 1907/08, 1935/36-1936/37, 1938/39-1941/42
- Addresses at the inauguration of Bryn Mawr College, 1885; 1 item(s) Bound with President's reports
- Graduate school, 1897-1970; 64 item(s) Programs for 1897/98, 1902-1915, 1917-1918, 1920-1963/64, 1965/66, 1968/69-1969/70
- Carola Woerishoffer Graduate Department of Social Economy and Social Research, 1916-1947; 12 item(s) Announcements for 1916, 1918-1919/20, 1923-1924, 1929, 1931, 1935/36-1937/38, 1946/47
  - Graduate courses in industrial supervision to meet the war emergency demand..., 1918; 1 item(s)
- Register of alumnae and former students, 1908; 1 item(s)
- Competitive matriculation scholarships, 1915; 1 item(s)
- Preliminary schedule of collegiate examinations, 1905-1906; 1 item(s)
- Institut d'etudes Francaises D'Avignon, 1965-1966; 2 item(s) Posters for 1965-1966
- Report Conference on the place of biological research in the liberal arts colleges, 1954; 1 item(s)
- Bryn Mawr Alumnae Bulletin, 1921-1946; 76 item(s) v. 1, #2, Feb. 1921-v. 3, #6, #8, #10, v. 4, 1924-v. 8, 1928, v. 9, #2. Feb. 1929, v. 27, #2 Dec. 1946